Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Course files, 1965 -- 2012; UA044.003; 22.8 Linear Feet
  - EXP 69S, Spring 1985: An Introduction to the United Nations, Sondra Torgerson, UA044.003.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - EXP 69F, Fall 1977: Alexander the Great, Reid Whitlock, UA044.003.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - EXP 69S, Spring 1976: Accounting for Non-Accountants, Barry Knamm, UA044.003.026.00027 (Box 26)
  - EXP 70S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Introduction to the Criminal Justice System, David Slater, UA044.003.026.00028 (Box 26)
  - EXP 70S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979: Architecture: an Overview, Jacquelinee Masloff, UA044.003.026.00029 (Box 26)
  - EXP 70F, Fall 1977: Gypsies, Leita Kaldi, UA044.003.026.00030 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71F, Fall 1985: Entrepreneurship, Ioannis Miaoulis, UA044.003.026.00031 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71F, Fall 1982: Marketing, Merchandising - Basic Fundamentals, Harold Bernstein, UA044.003.026.00032 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Introduction to American Law, Phillipe de Lacoste, UA044.003.026.00033 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71F, Fall 1976: Law and the Mentally Handicapped, William O'Neil, UA044.003.026.00034 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71S, Spring 1976: Discrimination and the Law, Marie Jackson, UA044.003.026.00035 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71F, Fall 1975: Women and the Law, Judith Freedman, UA044.003.026.00036 (Box 26)
  - EXP 71F, Fall (1969?-71?): Black Music, Cheryl Gail Williams and Stephen Morrow, 1969 -- 1971; UA044.003.026.00037 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1984: Business and International Affairs, Ethan Kapstein, UA044.003.026.00038 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1983: The Economics of Sports, Rob Sweren and Kevin Thurm, UA044.003.026.00039 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1982: Labor Law and Contract Negotiating, UA044.003.026.00040 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1981: Understanding Advertising, Jan Selby and Maura O'Shea, UA044.003.026.00041 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1979: Introduction to Health, Pamela Anderson and Nancy Kartz, UA044.003.026.00042 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1978: The Consumer and the Law, Bruce Keller, UA044.003.026.00043 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1977: Introduction to Criminal Law and Procedure, Peter DeGelleke, UA044.003.026.00044 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72F, Fall 1976: Women and the Law, Susan Thal and Lory Rosenbert, UA044.003.026.00045 (Box 26)
  - EXP 72S, Spring 1976: Psychology and the Law, Carolyn and James Topinka, UA044.003.026.00046 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73F, Fall 1985: Corporate Culture, Lawrence Levine, UA044.003.026.00047 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73S, Spring 1983 (EXP 73F): Strategic Planning, Management and Decision Making, James Hollowood, UA044.003.026.00048 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73F, Fall 1982: Anatomy of a Criminal Jury Trial, Peter DeGelleke, UA044.003.026.00049 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73F, Fall 1981: Labor Relations and the Law, Sherrie Talmadge, UA044.003.026.00050 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73F, Fall 1977: Criminal Court System, Elliot Lobel and Paul Waickowski, UA044.003.026.00051 (Box 26)
  - EXP 73S, Spring 1977: The American Legal System, Peter Irons, UA044.003.026.00052 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1987: Strategic Development, Gary Del Viscio, UA044.003.026.00053 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1983: Trading in Commodity Futures, Bruce Cohen, UA044.003.026.00054 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74F, Fall 1981: The Law and Social Inequality, Mark Coven, UA044.003.026.00055 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1981/Spring 1982: Introduction to Business Law, David Adelson, UA044.003.026.00056 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1978 (EXP 74F, Fall 1979): Introduction to Criminal Law and Procedure, Leonard Mandell, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.003.026.00057 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1979: Advertising Regulation, Bruce Keller, UA044.003.026.00058 (Box 26)
  - EXP 74S, Spring 1976: Supreme Court and Public Law, Todd Kanter and Leonard Nason, UA044.003.026.00059 (Box 26)
  - EXP 75F, Fall 1987: Looking at the City, Kiko Denzer, UA044.003.026.00060 (Box 26)
  - EXP 75S, Spring 1986/Spring 1986: Options and Futures: The Evolution of Capital Markets, Bruce Cohen, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.026.00061 (Box 26)
  - EXP 75S, Spring 1984: Consumer Rights and Remedies, Robert Gaines and John Donohue, UA044.003.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - EXP 75S, Spring 1983: The Art of Negotiation, Thomas Bean, UA044.003.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - EXP 76F, Fall 1987/Fall 1988: Making it in Massachusetts, Kadish (Spring 1989: Introduction to Stress Management, Elizabeth Dolan), 1987 -- 1989; UA044.003.027.00003 (Box 27)
    This file is empty
  - EXP 75S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Argumentation and Debate: How to Talk Anyone into Anything, Nan Bernstein and Peter Brann, UA044.003.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - EXP 76F, Fall 1985: Negotiation and Advocacy, Jamie Katz and Richard Heller, UA044.003.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - EXP 76S, Spring 1982: Merging the Courtroom with Theatre, Jerry Collins, Elliot Lobel and Daina Robins, UA044.003.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - EXP 76S, Spring 1980: Management for Young Professionals, Robert Reiner, UA044.003.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - EXP 76S, Spring 1976: The World of John and Abigail, Carol Levin, UA044.003.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - EXP 77F, Fall 1992/Spring 1993: The Politics of Health Care Reform, Laurie Cammisa, 1992 -- 1993; UA044.003.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - EXP 77F, Fall 1983: Practical Labor Relations, Edward Perry, UA044.003.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - EXP 77S, Spring 1980: Stocks and Bonds, Leonard Loventhal, UA044.003.027.00011 (Box 27)
  - EXP 77S, Spring 1976: Fanasty and Faith, Rick Tilden, UA044.003.027.00012 (Box 27)
  - EXP 78S, Spring 1997: Seminar on Negotiation and Conflict Resolution, Rhoda Margesson, UA044.003.027.00013 (Box 27)
  - EXP 78S, Spring 1984/Fall 1984/Spring 1985: Juvenile Justice, Robert Clayman, 1984 -- 1985; UA044.003.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - EXP 78S, Spring 1983: Judge or Jury, Lyman Stookey, UA044.003.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - EXP 78S, Spring 1976: Black Religious Consciousness, D. Keith Naylor, UA044.003.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80F, Fall 1998: Business Ethics, Lisa Allen, UA044.003.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80S, Spring 1992/Spring 1993: Business Policy, Mark Bamford, 1992 -- 1993; UA044.003.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80F, Fall 1988: Rights to Life, Rights to Die, Kevin Brill, UA044.003.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80S, Spring 1988: Rehnquist vs. Warren: Legal Theory in the 1990s, Kevin Brill, UA044.003.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80F, Fall 1980: Senior Seminar: Writers and Revolution, Poetry and Politics, Sol Gittleman, UA044.003.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80F, Fall 1979: Senior Seminar: Sickness and Health, Fred Shepler, UA044.003.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - EXP 80F, Fall 1978: Senior Seminar, Jack Tessman, UA044.003.027.00023 (Box 27)
    this folder is empty
  - EXP 81S, Spring 1981: Senior Seminar: Intellectual Revolutions in Science and Art, Gary Goldstein, UA044.003.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - EXP 81S, Spring 1980: Senior Seminar: Integrations, Jesper Rosenmeier, UA044.003.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - EXP 81F, Fall 1969: Politics of Non-Violent Action, Gene Sharp, UA044.003.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - EXP 82F, Fall 1989: News Media and the Law, Charles Goldsmith, UA044.003.027.00027 (Box 27)
  - EXP 82F, Fall 1988: Justice at Work, Gary Altman, UA044.003.027.00028 (Box 27)
  - EXP 82S, Spring 1986: Quidnunc: On Gender Issues: The Male and Female Image, Grete Viddal and David Komet, UA044.003.027.00029 (Box 27)
  - EXP 82S, Spring 1978: Sleep and Dreams, Barry Skoff and Diane Russ, UA044.003.027.00030 (Box 27)
  - EXP 83S, Spring 1976: Man Adapting, Leighton Reynolds, UA044.003.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - EXP 84F, Fall 1988/Fall 1989: Negotiation, Harvey Cotton and Deborah Welsh, 1988 -- 1989; UA044.003.027.00032 (Box 27)
  - EXP 84S, Spring 1976: Thematic Crossword Puzzle Construction, Marjorie Pedersen, UA044.003.027.00033 (Box 27)
  - EXP 85S, Spring 1986: Soviet-American Relations 1917-1986: Semyon Appatov, UA044.003.027.00034 (Box 27)
  - EXP 85S, Spring 1980: Leadership Seminar, Bobbie Knable, UA044.003.027.00035 (Box 27)
  - EXP 86S, Spring 1978: Development of Interpersonal Communication, Gary Drake, UA044.003.027.00036 (Box 27)
  - EXP 88S, Spring 1983: Stirring the Melting Pot, Part II, Bobbie Knable, UA044.003.027.00037 (Box 27)
  - EXP 88S, Spring 1978: African-American Psychological Identity, Tommie Samkange, UA044.003.027.00038 (Box 27)
  - EXP 89F, Fall 1982: Stirring the Melting Pot: Issues of Gender, Class, Race, Bobbie Knable, UA044.003.027.00039 (Box 27)
  - EXP 89S, Spring 1978: Intermediate Bridge Play, Joe Adlman, UA044.003.027.00040 (Box 27)
  - EXP 89F, Fall 1976: Tutoring at Columbia Point, Paul Johnson and Elliott Temple, UA044.003.027.00041 (Box 27)
  - EXP 91F, Fall 1976: Residential Staff Course, Bruce Reitman, UA044.003.027.00042 (Box 27)
  - EXP 91S, Spring 1976: School Desegregation, George Cox, UA044.003.027.00043 (Box 27)
    lable on folder originally read "EXP 93S Spring 1976"
  - EXP 92S, Spring 1983: Praise of Teaching, Lucille Palubinskas, UA044.003.027.00044 (Box 27)
  - EXP 94S, Spring 1983: Study and Testing Aid, Deborah Greenwald and David Harder, UA044.003.027.00045 (Box 27)
  - EXP 94S, Spring 1976: Misuse and Abuse of Children, Fern Creelan, UA044.003.027.00046 (Box 27)
  - EXP 95S, Spring 1987: Acting Workshop, Bill Reichblum, UA044.003.027.00047 (Box 27)
  - EXP 95S, Spring 1982: Short-Term Studies: Commedia Dell'Arte Techniques for the Actor, Don Jordon, UA044.003.027.00048 (Box 27)
  - EXP 95S, Spring 1971/Fall 1971: Teaching English as a Foreign Language, Arthur Chiasson, UA044.003.027.00049 (Box 27)
  - EXP 97S, Spring 1988: Quidnunc: Social Movements and the Individual: from 1968-1988 and to the Future, UA044.003.027.00050 (Box 27)
  - EXP 97F, Fall 1986: Quidnunc: South Africa, UA044.003.027.00051 (Box 27)
  - EXP 97F, Fall 1985: Terrorism, Political Violence Colloquium, UA044.003.027.00052 (Box 27)
  - EXP 99F, Fall 1998: Women's Studies Internship, UA044.003.027.00053 (Box 27)
  - EXP 102S, Spring 1972: Participant in Discovery, Edward Maly, UA044.003.027.00054 (Box 27)
  - EXP 190S, Spring 1981: Group Independent Study: Survey of Armenian History, Raffi Hovanissian, UA044.003.027.00055 (Box 27)
    label on folder reads "EXP 190AS"
  - EXP 190S, Spring 1981: Group Independent Study: The Effects of Contemporary Life on the Black Family, Patrick Barclay and Sandra Greer, UA044.003.027.00056 (Box 27)
    label on folder reads "EXP 190BS"
  - EXP 190S, Spring 1981: Group Independent Study: The Asian-American Experience and Identity, Sandy Leung, UA044.003.027.00057 (Box 27)
    label on folder reads "EXP 190CS"
  - EXP 190S, Spring 1981: Group Independent Study: Advanced Japanese, UA044.003.027.00058 (Box 27)
    label on folder reads, "EXP 190DS"
  - EXP 190F, Fall 1980: Senior Explorations: Women's Changing Roles in Judaism, UA044.003.027.00059 (Box 27)
  - EXP 190S, Spring 1980: Quidnunc: Group Independent Study, UA044.003.027.00060 (Box 27)
  - EXP 192S, Spring 1981: Independent Study: Chemistry Topics, Robert Yohai, UA044.003.027.00061 (Box 27)
  - EXP 192Z, Summer 1978: Optical Printing, Jon Rubin, UA044.003.027.00062 (Box 27)
  - Jumbo in Color, 2012; UA044.003.028.00001; Meyers, Risa T.; This is a watercolor of Jumbo in a spectrum of colors. I took advantage of the watercolor medium by making water blossoms and diluting paints to blend colors to create the elephant's form. This painting is part of a series of studies of elephants as well as a collection of work using the colorwheel as a tool.
    This is a watercolor of Jumbo in a spectrum of colors. I took advantage of the watercolor medium by making water blossoms and diluting paints to blend colors to create the elephant's form. This painting is part of a series of studies of elephants as well as a collection of work using the colorwheel as a tool.
  - Jumbo's Tail, 2012; UA044.003.028.00002; Ono, Misako
    graphite and color pencils on paper
  - Course Files: Numbers EXP 02 S to EXP 27 F, 1990 -- 1995; UA044.003.029 (Box 29)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Course Files: Numbers EXP 27 S to EXP 87 S, 1990 -- 1995; UA044.003.030 (Box 30)
- Annual reports, 1970 -- 1996; UA044.004; 1 Linear Feet
  This series contains the Experimental College's annual reports between the years 1970 and 1996.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Annual report, 1970 -- 1971; UA044.001940 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1971 -- 1972; UA044.001941 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 1972 -- 1973; UA044.001942 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Annual report, 1973 -- 1974; UA044.001943 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Annual report, 1974 -- 1975; UA044.001944 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Annual report, 1975 -- 1976; UA044.001945 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Annual report, 1976 -- 1977; UA044.001946 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Annual report, 1977 -- 1978; UA044.001947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Annual report, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.001948 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Annual report, 1979 -- 1980; UA044.001949 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Annual report, 1980 -- 1981; UA044.001950 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Annual report, 1981 -- 1982; UA044.001951 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Annual report, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001952 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Annual report, 1983 -- 1984; UA044.001953 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Annual report, 1984 -- 1985; UA044.001954 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Annual report, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.001955 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA044.001956 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA044.001957 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Annual report, 1988 -- 1989; UA044.001958 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Annual report, 1989 -- 1990; UA044.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1990 -- 1991; UA044.001959 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Annual report, 1990 -- 1991; UA044.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1991 -- 1992; UA044.001960 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Annual report, 1991 -- 1992; UA044.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1992 -- 1993; UA044.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1993 -- 1994; UA044.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1994 -- 1995; UA044.004.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Annual report, 1995 -- 1996; UA044.004.017.00007 (Box 17)